{"data":[{"question":"Moira lives ____ Toronto.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Turn left ____ the traffic lights.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Ernest works ____ an office","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Gerhard buys things ____ flea markets.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Put the papers ___ the desk please.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"I met Christine _____ university.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Don't believe everything you read _____ newspapers.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- We often say \" in newspaper\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Christian isn't here. He's ____ work.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n \n- At work: a place where you do your job, which is not your home\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"Kurt's office is ____ the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"},{"question":"There were a lot of people _____ the party.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"2"}]}